[ Background Sounds ]
[ 背景音 ]
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Hi, everyone.
&gt;&gt; 嗨 大家好
My name is Carolyn Cranfill and
我叫 Carolyn Cranfill
I'm a designer on the Human
是 Apple 人机界面组的
Interface Team, here at Apple.
一名设计师
And I also lead the inclusive
也领导了包容性设计的
design efforts.
工作
Thank you for joining us today.
谢谢你们今天的到来
We released a series of seven
上个月
videos last month highlighting
我们陆续发布了七个视频
people who feel empowered to do
着重刻画了那些因为做着自己喜欢的事情
what they love.
而充满能量的人们
And I'd like to share with you
现在我想和你们分享
one right now.
其中一个
&gt;&gt; At first, my motivation was
Carols：刚开始我只是想
proving people wrong.
证明人们错了
&gt;&gt; Accessibility.
VoiceOver：辅助功能
Vision. Voiceover.
视觉 Voiceover
Font.
开启
Scheduled arriving.
计划到达
Second location.
第二个地点
&gt;&gt; We don't want our first album
Carols：我们不希望我们的第一张专辑
to sound like a local band.
听上去像本地乐队
&gt;&gt; ETA 10 minutes.
VoiceOver：预计 10 分钟到达
&gt;&gt; We wanted our first album to
Carols：我们希望我们的第一张专辑
sound like a professional band
听上去更像一个专业乐队
that's been doing it for years.
我们已经为此努力了很多年
&gt;&gt; Requesting a ride and
VoiceOver：发送搭车请求
connecting to nearby drivers.
正在联系附近司机
Finding a ride.
找到可用车
&gt;&gt; [Drumming] We're called
[ 鼓声 ]
Distartica and we play heavy
Carols：我们叫 Distartica
metal.
我们演奏重金属音乐
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
&gt;&gt; Turn left onto Empanada
Siri：左转进入
Drive.
Empanada 车道
&gt;&gt; Empanada?
Man：[ 笑 ] Empanada（肉馅卷饼）
&gt;&gt; Empanada Drive.
Carols：Empanada 车道
&gt;&gt; That makes me hungry.
Man：我听着都饿了[ 笑 ]
&gt;&gt; I ended up becoming the PR
Carols：我最终成为了乐队的
manager in the band.
公关经理
Like I didn't get what it was
我以前不知道这个工作是
before.
做什么的
Yeah man, like oh, dude.
然后我就是这样的
Like hashtag why?
为什么要打标签
Like What?
要做什么
Hashtag metal.
#金属
Hashtag new music.
#新音乐
Or, you know on this case like
或者在这种情况下
hashtag like debut album.
要写#debut album 之类的
&gt;&gt; Messages.
VoiceOver：信息
ReverbNation.
来自 ReverbNation
Double tap to open.
双击以打开
Text field.
文本框
Dictate.
听写
&gt;&gt; Album will be dropping
Carols：专辑将在 2017 年 4 月 14 日
worldwide on April 14, 2017!
全球发行 感叹号
Follow our ReverbNation page.
关注我们的 ReverbNation 页面 句号
&gt;&gt; Done. Successfully shared.
[ 点按 ]VoiceOver：完成 已成功分享
[ Music ]
[ 音乐 ]
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; So, this film, along with the
因此从这个视频可以看出
others beautifully depicts the
这系列影片生动的刻画了
impact accessible tech has on
当你为每个人
people's lives when you design
包括一定程度残疾的人做设计时
for everyone, including people
这些可用的科技
with a range of disabilities.
会对人们的生活造成多么大的影响
I'm here today to ask you to
我今天在这里
join the campaign with us in
是希望你们加入我们
designing your apps and games to
设计人人可用的
work for everyone too.
App 和游戏
Because we inherently design for
因为我们的天性是
ourselves, because we design to
为自己做设计
what we know, our own world
设计反映出我们的见闻觉知
view.
反映出我们的世界观
We have wants and needs, and
我们有需求
passions.
和激情
We think of features, make an
我们想出点子制作 App
app, join a company to put those
加入公司
ideas out there for others too.
将想法传递给他人
But regardless, the next step of
但无论如何
reaching more people is putting
下一步要想推广给更多的人
yourself in their shoes.
就必须为他们着想
We need to figure out who we
我们需要知道
might be excluding.
是-否有可能遗漏的顾客
Have you thought about how there
你有没有想过
might be other people out in the
世界上还有一些人
world with the same passions,
有着和你一样的
needs and wants as you, but
激情和需求
can't use your app?
却不能使用你的 App
If we think about how there are
想一想全世界
more than one billion active
现在有超过十亿
Apple devices out there, which
活跃的 Apple 设备
is a lot of potential customers,
潜在顾客人数是很惊人的
and knowing that one in seven
再想想
people in the world have a
全世界每七个人中就有一人
disability, we can be sure that
身患残疾
people who may want to use our
我相信
apps and platforms will lie
想使用你的 App 和平台的人
everywhere across a spectrum of
遍布世界各地
abilities and capabilities.
身体状况与能力各不相同
Human abilities vary greatly
不同的人
across cognition and social
在认知 社交能力
abilities; dexterity, mobility,
敏捷性 机动性
vision and hearing.
视力和听力方面都有着巨大差距
And in order to understand and
而我们通过
comprehend information, our
视觉 听觉和触觉的感知而获得的官能
perception through sight, sound
是理解和领会信息
and touch are essential.
的关键
What happens if you inhibit one
如果你先天或后天
of those senses, or take one
失去了这些官能
away?
会怎样呢
That could happen to you or I in
这是可能发生
our lifetime, gradually or
在你我身上的
instantaneously.
可能缓慢发生 也有可能突然而至
People with physical
身体残疾
disabilities will include
包括一些极端的例子
extreme cases, like cerebral
比如脑瘫和
palsy and paralysis, but also
瘫痪
include conditions like carpal
也包括腕管综合征
tunnel syndrome, or temporary
或
conditions such as a broken
手腕扭伤
wrist.
等暂时性病症
People with vision loss will
视力丧失包括
include blindness, low vision,
失明 视力低下
and colorblindness.
和色盲
But also, situational
但也包括
disabilities like screen glare
暂时性的屏幕炫光
and temporary day blindness that
和暂时性昼盲
we all experience when emerging
就像我们每次
from a dark movie theater.
从黑暗的电影院走出来时经历的那样
Hearing loss is one of the
听力丧失是
leading types of hearing
一种典型的
disabilities.
听觉障碍
Whether it's from birth or it's
无论是先天的
prevalent with age, made for
还是随着年纪增长造成的
iPhone hearing aids are changing
iPhone 助听工具
people's quality of life.
提高了人们的生活质量
And as we extend our
我们也将所有的
notification queues to having
视觉 口头表达和触觉反馈
all visual, oral, and tactile
列入通知方式的队列中
feedback, we're enabling
让所有人
everyone to get their
都能够
notifications.
得到通知
And you may have heard the
你可能听到过
statistic that 1 in 68 children
疾病防治中心的
in the United States have been
数据反馈
identified with the autism
美国每六十八个孩子中
spectrum disorder, according to
就有一个孩子
the CDC.
被确诊为儿童自闭症
Autistic individuals can be
自闭个体
sensitive to unexpected sounds
对突然的声音和
and distracting graphics.
纷乱的图形非常敏感
And there are also many adults
也有一些大人和孩子
and children with dyslexia.
患有阅读障碍
Having multiple visual and
多种视觉和听觉选项
auditory options help people
给患有阅读障碍的人
with dyslexia and is also widely
带来了帮助
used by the blind and people
也得到了失明和视力低下人群的
with low vision.
广泛使用
So, if we think about how
如果我们考虑到
everyone in the world will have
世界上的每一个人
a range of abilities and
不同的
capabilities, the next step of
身体状况和能力
reaching more people is making
扩大影响力的下一步
your apps accessible.
就是使你的 App 可用
But the word accessible wasn't
可用一词
invented to describe
并不是专指
accommodating those with
满足残疾人的
disabilities.
需求
It's about access, whoever we
而是让所有的人
are.
都能够使用
Easily reached or obtained.
轻松获得
Easily used.
轻松使用
Easily understood.
轻松理解
Everyone. Whether you have a
每一个人
permanent or situational
不管是不是有长期或短期的障碍
impairment, young or old, new or
年纪如何
pro to technology.
对技术是否精通
Whatever language you sign,
使用何种语言书写
speak, or read would love access
交谈或阅读
to great apps.
都能够使用的卓越的 App
Together, we can design better
大家一起参与
apps for everyone.
我们可以设计出更好的 App 让每一个人都能使用
To help you do this, we're going
为了给你们提供帮助
to talk about some design
我们会介绍一些
considerations and workflow
设计考量和工作流程技术
techniques to keep in mind when
这是你们在制作
making your apps work for more
让更多人使用的 App 时
people.
需要考虑的
By being inclusive, not only can
通过包容性设计
we help everyone function in
我们不仅能帮助
their daily life.
每个人的日常生活
But we can also create new
还能为
possibilities throughout
整个社会
society.
创造新的可能
So, today, we're going to talk
因此今天我们要介绍的
about three areas of designing
是为所有人设计的
for everyone.
三个方面
Striving for simplicity, making
力求简洁
our apps effortless and easy to
让顾客能够轻松自如的
learn.
学习使用我们的 App
Accessing perceivability.
感知访问
Making sure our apps are
确保我们的 App
understandable through sight,
是通过视觉
sound, and haptics.
听觉和触觉可理解的
And designing with integrity.
和正直设计
Holding ourselves accountable
在道德上负责
for ethically making sure we
确保
include everyone.
考虑到所有人
These are principles applied to
这是提供更好顾客体验
making great experiences,
需要遵循的原则
period.
句号
So, first if we think about
因此首先我们要想到的
something that is simple to do,
是简单
we think of it being effortless
操作必须毫不费力
without difficulties, hurdles,
没有困难障碍
or cognitive strain.
和认知负担
But for something to feel simple
但是简单
that does mean it can't do
并不意味着不能完成
complex things.
复杂的事情
It just means trying to achieve
只是要以
desired outcomes in the most
最轻松简洁的方式
effortless and elegant way
得到
possible.
想要的结果
Things that aren't simple create
如果不够简单
barriers of entry to everyone.
会为每一个试图尝试的人制造障碍
As we go through our day, the
在我们辛苦了一天之后
requirements of work and life
来自工作和生活的要求
slowly drains our energy.
慢慢耗尽了我们的精力
And when we are low on energy,
而当我们没什么精神的时候
we have less energy to
就更没精力
troubleshoot tech and less
接触麻烦的技术
patience for navigating
也没耐心去操作那些
something that should be quick
本该便捷
and easy.
的东西了
At night, we rest and recharge.
我们在晚上放松自己恢复精力
However, were you aware that one
但你有没有意识到
in six children in the United
美国
States have a developmental
每六个孩子中就有一个
disability?
有发展性障碍
It ranges from mild
从轻度的
disabilities, such as speech and
言语和语言障碍
language impairments to serious
到重度的
developmental disabilities, such
智力障碍
as intellectual disabilities and
和
autism.
自闭症
For people who have cognitive
对于那些有
disabilities and/or chronic
认知障碍和/或慢性疾病的人来说
illnesses, they might start out
他们每天的精力
the day at three-quarters of a
本身就不及
tank.
常人
And tasks take extra effort
一整天的任务
throughout the day.
还会消耗额外的精力
Plus, if you exert yourself all
再加上
the way to empty on one day, you
如果你前一天精疲力竭
might start out the next day,
第二天也就可能
extremely low.
很疲乏
So, the apps that we make do a
我们制作的 App
great job at helping us through
能够很好的帮助人们
our day.
度过每一天
Whether it's a convenience or
无论是让生活更方便
helping us to recharge.
还是帮助我们恢复精力
They provide quick and easy
这些 App 让人们
access to services, which is
能够轻松快捷地获得服务
extremely important for those
这对那些
who may have difficulty
走出家门非常困难
traveling outside of the home,
用电话交谈困难
speaking a hearing on the phone,
或同时兼顾工作和家庭生活的人来说
or juggling work and home life.
非常重要
For example, convenience apps
比如像 Instacart
like Instacart, you can have
这样方便的 App
groceries delivered to your door
可以将食品杂货送上门
which alleviates the stress of
既减轻了
the supermarket, or allows you
超市的压力
to rest at home.
也让你可以在家休息
Or maybe it just gives you time
或者为你留出了
back with your family.
与家人相伴的时间
With education apps like
使用如 Duolingo 的教育类 App
Doulingo it's incredible that we
可以让我们舒适的在家中学习
can learn from the comforts of
按照自己的时间
our home, on our own time, at
和自己的速度安排进度
our own speed, and with health
非常神奇
apps like Calm, they help us
如 Calm 的健康类 App
nurture our mental and physical
帮助锻炼了我们的
well-being.
心理和生理健康
And with content creation apps
使用像 iMovie 的内容创造类 App
like iMovie, we can create and
我们可以创造并
share our artistry with friends,
与朋友家人和全世界
family and the world.
分享我们的艺术才华
So, apps play a key role in our
因此 App 在我们如今的生活中
daily lives now.
扮演了关键的角色
And we can make even more impact
我们可以通过
in people's lives by reducing
减少人们使用我们 App 耗费的精力
the amount of effort that we
减少障碍
require to use our apps, which
提供更多的接触机会
reduces barriers and provides
从而进一步地
more access.
影响人们的生活
But this is easier said than
话是这么说
done.
实现起来并不容易
So here are some ideas.
这里有一些可以采用的建议
We should strive for our apps to
为了使 App 容易操作
be easy to navigate by having
我们要努力让我们的 App
them similarly structured.
具有类似的结构
We need to be able to get
我们需要使
started and complete common task
顾客在开始和完成普通任务时
without encountering any
不会遇到任何
barriers or issues.
障碍或问题
And we should use UIKit as much
我们应尽可能多的使用 UIKit
as possible to achieve the
以便
consistent behaviors within each
在每个 App 内及不同 App 间
app and across apps.
实现行为的一致性
Because UIKit wasn't made for
因为 UIKit 不是仅仅
just developers.
为开发人员而做的
It's a design language for the
它是平台上的设计语言
platform that everyone is
每个人都熟悉
familiar with and knows how to
并且知道如何
use.
使用
And there are design resources
这里有一些关于人机界面准则的
on human interface guidelines to
设计资源
help you use the standard UIKit
可以帮助你在设计阶段
components in your apps during
在 App 中
the design phase.
使用标准 UIKit 组件
It's important to remember that
重要的是要记住
these toolkits support many
这些工具支持很多
accessibility accommodations.
辅助功能
And if we can consistently use
如果我们一直使用
standard UIKit interaction
标准 UIKit 交互
patterns and components for more
模式和组件
task of our apps like basic
完成我们 App 中越来越多的任务
structure and navigation,
如基本结构和操作
sign-up flows, account settings,
注册帐户设置和分享
and sharing then you can spend
那么你-就可以把
the majority of your time on the
大部分时间
parts of your apps that make
放在你 App
them special.
独特的部分上
And making sure those parts are
确保这些部分也是
accessible too.
可进入的
Consistent use of our design
持续使用我们的设计语言
language is beneficial because
是非常有好处的
if you learn one app you have a
因为如果你学习了一个 App
serious head start on learning
就等于在学习其他 App 上也有优势
another because repetition
因为重复会
creates cognitive ease and a
减轻认知压力
comforting feeling of
并让人-获得
familiarity.
熟悉的舒适感
But we know it's not always
但我们知道只用 UIKit
possible, to solely use UIKit.
并不总是可行的
There are times when you need to
有时你需要
do something unique and
完成独特原创的东西
original, but don't forget about
但不要忘记
accessibility.
可进入性
It makes you think more
这会让你对
holistically about the products
即将发行的产品
that you're putting out into the
有更加整体的
world.
思考
So, simplicity.
因此简洁
Building on what I know.
根据已知进行构建
Making use of standard
使用标准组件
components and familiar
和熟悉的
interaction patterns to help
交互模式
make apps easy to navigate.
可以帮助 App 更易操作
Be laser focused in your
要专心于
objectives.
你的目标
Reduce any hurdles.
去掉所有的障碍
Help me get started quickly.
帮助顾客快速入门
And it just works like I
它就像我预想的那样
expected it to consistently.
一直运行良好
So, our products need to be
因此我们的产品
understandable and perceivable
需要被所有人
to everyone.
理解和感知
This means that information
这就意味着
needs to be available to at
信息至少要以
least one sense; sight, sound or
一种感觉
touch that is available to each
视觉 听觉 触觉中的一种
person.
传递给每一个人
And we can look at our apps and
我们可以看一下自己的 App
ask ourselves is it legible?
问自己它清楚易读吗
Is it audible?
它有声音吗
And is it tactile?
它可以被触摸吗
But before we look at
但在关注易读性
legibility.
之前
Let's escape for a moment to
让我们抽出一点时间
this beautiful beach and
来到这个美丽的沙滩
experience it in a few different
通过一些不同的方法
ways.
进行体验
Relax, watch the waves roll in
放松看
and out.
潮来潮去
Soak up that sunshine for a
短暂的感受
second.
阳光
And if you have vision loss, you
如果你患有视力丧失
might not get to see this in all
可能无法完全看到
of its glory, but you're hearing
沙滩美丽的风景
would be more sensitive to these
但你的听力会比较敏锐
beautiful sounds.
可以听到动听的声音
[ Ocean Sounds ]
[ 海洋声 ]
Or if you're colorblind, you
如果你是色盲
might see the world more like
你眼中的世界
this.
可能更类似于这样
Or if you're blind, you're
或者如果你是盲人
likely even more in-tune to the
那你对声音
sound.
可能就更加敏锐
And these situations are very
这些场景
real.
是真实的
In the world, 285 million people
据估计全世界有
are estimated to have moderate
2.85 亿人患有
or severe vision loss.
轻度或重度的视力丧失
And 39 million of those are
其中有三千九百万
completely blind.
完全失明
And one in 12 men are
每十二位男性中
colorblind.
就有一位是色盲
And best estimates are around
保守估计全世界有
360 million people in the world
3.6 亿人
have disabling hearing loss.
患有听力丧失
Not only can hearing and vision
听力和视力丧失
loss limit people from
不仅会限制人们
distinguishing information, but
辨别信息的能力
they will also be seeing and
还会在很多你想不到的地方
hearing your brand in different
影响你
ways than you expected.
听到和看到的东西
For example, someone with low
比如说
vision may see their phones like
视力低下的人眼中的手机
this.
是这样的
And if you aren't low vision
如果你自己本身视力良好
yourself, you can simulate low
你可以设计软件中的
vision by using a small blur in
模糊功能
your design software.
模拟视力低下
Now, people with low vision will
现在视力低下的人
often learn the location of
只有在不动的时候
icons as long as they don't
才能看清商标
move.
的位置
But content areas are different.
但内容范围就不一样了
So, they need to maintain high
他们需要维持高度的视觉对比
visual contrast to increase
提高
legibility.
易读性
So, if you get started, you
如果你刚刚起步
should ask yourself is your app
那你应该问问自己
legible?
我的 App 易读吗
Because maximizing legibility is
因为最大化易读性
the highest benefit on being
对理解信息
able to comprehend information
最有帮助
because it's less work on us to
因为我们要做的解读
interpret.
工作会变少
For example, when we have key
比如
information that is low in
如果我们的关键信息
contrasts because of small fonts
因为字体太小
and low color contrast ratios,
色彩对比率太低
or thin fonts.
或字体过瘦而对比度很低
It may be painful to read and
阅读起来就会很痛苦
you experience cognitive strain.
也会加重你的认知负担
So, a good place to start to
所以改掉低对比度
correct low contrast is to use
一个很好的方法是
the default textile body for
为你的主要内容
your main content and a high
使用默认的 Textile Body
color contrast with your
并选择与背景
background.
对比强烈的颜色
And then you can use bolder font
接着你可以使用粗体
weights to emphasize text or
强调文本和标题
titles, rather than thin fonts.
而不是常规的字体
And you can use filled in button
你可以使用对按钮图形使用填充
shapes so that the text contrast
这样文本对比会很高
is high, and the way forward in
如何在你的 App 中更进一步
your app is really clear.
也非常清楚
And if you don't use textiles or
如果你在 App 中没有使用
system fonts in your app, it
Textile 和系统字体
would be ideal to support the
那么支持
accessibility bold text
辅助功能中的粗体设置
settings, which requires you to
是很理想的方法
increase your font weights by
当开启该设置时
two weights thicker when the
你需要将你的字体
setting is on.
加粗两号
Now, this is built-in with
现在它已经与
system fonts and textiles.
系统字体和 Textile 一起内嵌了
The new App Store design does an
全新 App Store 设计
excellent job at maximizing
在最大化易读性方面做得非常好
legibility through its bold
它使用了加粗字体
typography, prominent buy
突出购买按钮
buttons, large fonts, and high
字体加大
color contrast colors.
和高色彩对比度的颜色
Great job guys.
干得漂亮伙伴们
On macOS, there are increased
在 macOS 上
contrast settings as well, that
也有提高对比度的设置
when on all active controls
开启时
become higher contrast by making
所有 Active 控件的对比度都会提高
backgrounds opaque, button
背景会透明
outlines becomes thicker and
按钮外框会加粗加深
darker and system colors become
系统颜色也会变得更深
darker to create high color
从而创造出
contrast ratios.
高色彩对比率
So now that you know to look
现在知道重点之后
for, let's look at the before
让我们再次看一下调整前后的
and after again.
对比
Before.
调整前
After.
调整后
And even the ruled lines and the
甚至灰色文本的
color values of gray text
边框和颜色
becomes darker.
都变深了
You will need to supply these
你需要使用相同的
same alternate designs, if you
替代性设计
do not use standard AppKit
如果你不使用标准 AppKit 的话
because they will not come for
因为虽然它们在
free in custom UI, but they're
顾客 UI 中并不是免费的
extremely important for
但对于最大化易读性
maximizing legibility.
非常重要
Now, the next suggestion to
下一条
increase legibility maybe the
提高易读性的建议
most important thing to take
可能也是今天
away today.
最重要的一条建议
And that's to support dynamic
那就是支持动态类型
type, or the text size setting
或字体设置
because this feature increases
因为该功能可以提高易读性
legibility by allowing each
它可以
person to personalize their
让每个人通过调整
experience by increasing the
字体大小
font size.
个性化体验
Or, maybe you need a farther
或者你需要更远的观看距离
viewing distance if mounted on a
比如
chair or propped on a table.
固定在椅子上或者桌子上
Because when our fonts don't
因为当字体无法调整时
scale, people with low vision
视力低下的人
need to use screen zoom windows
需要缩放窗口
to read the content.
从而阅读内容
That's like having to turn your
这就像开灯
light on, or your magnifier in a
或者在昏暗的饭店里
dimly lit restaurant to read the
使用放大镜
menu.
阅读菜单
But except this is all day and
只是不会
every day.
整天这么做而已
And some people don't bother
对有些人来说
with zoom windows at all.
缩放窗口不算什么
They painfully read the small
他们短时间
type or use their phones for
阅读小字或使用手机
short periods of time.
都会很痛苦
And that's not a great
这是
experience.
不太愉快的经历
So, if you adopt dynamic type by
如果你采用动态类型
using textiles and use the new
使用 Textiles 和
standard spacing constraints, we
标准空格限制
can offer a larger reading
我们可以在
experience without needing zoom
无需缩放窗口的情况下
windows.
提供更好的阅读体验
And new this year in iOS 11 is
今年 iOS 11 新推出的是
dynamic type support for custom
支持顾客字体的
fonts.
动态类型
Additionally, if you access
除此之外
larger text setting via the
如果你通过“通用设置”
general settings, there's a
进入扩大字体的设置
switch that enables even larger
有一个开关能让你
accessibility text sizes.
进一步放大辅助字体
And this year, in iOS 11, all
今年在 iOS 11 中
textiles will support these
Textile 将支持
larger settings.
进一步放大的设置
So, this means that we need to
因此这就意味着我们需要
design responsive layouts to be
设计响应性的布局
able to handle these large font
从而能够处理
sizes.
大字体
To do this for our own platform
今年为了在我们的平台 App 上实现这一点
apps this year, a team of us
有一组同事
took a step back and developed a
退了一步
few simple principles that
开发出一些简单的原则
helped guide us through a
能够帮助我们完成
system-wide audit.
全系统的检测
The first principle was to make
第一条原则就是
as much text dynamic as possible
尽可能更多地使用文字动态
and to support these
并且支持
accessibility text sizes.
辅助字体
Next is make good use of the
第二条是更好的使用
screen width by wrapping lines
屏幕宽度
of type, rather than truncating.
绕排文本而不是截断文本
And then, displaying the same
然后在大字体情况下
amount of text at the larger
显示的文本数量
sizes as with the default UI.
要与默认 UI 中一致
And lastly, scaling glyphs that
最后调整
appear next to text in content
文本中符号的大小
areas so that the glyphs scale
让它们与文本
with the text in harmony.
和谐显示
And when we look at all of these
在实际情况中
together in practice it really
当我们综合考虑所有的原则时
gets magical.
会得到神奇的效果
The mail screen now grows the
在邮件窗口中
whole mail message to a zoom
现在整个邮件信息已经
level of 315% from the default
缩放为默认大小的
size.
315%
And in custom layouts, like
在日历等自定义布局中
calendar, this year we made even
今年我们做了更多的内容缩放
more content scale like the
比如
month grid increase in size,
月网格已经扩大
where it didn't support dynamic
之前它并不支持
type it all before.
动态类型
And at the larger accessibility
在更大的辅助字体中
sizes, we re-laid out the event
我们重新排列的事件行
row similar to the watch layout.
使之更接近 watch 的布局
Because in the end, the
因为最后
character count per line was
每行的字数
about the same.
是相同的
And it allowed maximum screen
现在文本也支持
width for text.
最大的屏幕宽度
So, now if we turn on the bold
现在如果我们开启
text setting and simulate low
粗体设置
vision with the blur, and
使用模糊模拟视力低下
compare it next to the largest
并将它与
currently shipping screen on the
左边目前放大到最大的屏幕进行比较
left, now people with vision
现在视力低下的人
loss will be able to use this
能够更轻松的
app more.
使用 App 了
Thanks.
谢谢
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
We've designed these responsive
我们已经在
layouts in most native UIKit
绝大部分自带的 UIKit 控件中
controls.
设计了这样的响应性布局
For example, like action sheets,
比如操作列表
edit menus, and a keyboard auto
编辑菜单和
correction bar.
键盘自动更正栏
For elements like navigation
像导航栏 工具栏 标签栏
bars, toolbars, and tab bars
等元素
that would take up too much
如果进行缩放
space if we scaled them.
会占据很大的空间
We added a larger representation
我们在主控中
of the Fortis in a central hub
添加了 Fortis 的大图标
that you can get via Long Press.
你可以长按进入
And we also added larger
我们也为分段控件
popovers for segmented controls.
添加了更大的弹出框
And we've also extended larger
我们也将这种放大的技术
tech support to system spaces
扩展到支持系统空间
like home screen app labels, and
比如主屏幕 App 标签
notifications.
和通知
Now, there are a few we missed
今年我们还有一些没有完成的
this year, but we have plans for
但我们已经有更多计划
more and if you support iKit,
如果你支持 iKit
you will get these updates for
你将在我们制作完成的第一时间
free as we make them.
免费获得更新
So, maximizing legibility and
最大化易读性
providing scalable dynamic type
以及提供可缩放的动态类型
improves visual experience for
能够提高每个人的
everyone.
视觉体验
And alongside text that is clear
除了文本要
and understandable, same applies
清晰可理解之外
for media and games.
媒体和游戏也是如此
All dialogue should support
所有对话都应支持
captions because captions
字幕
display what is being spoken,
因为字幕显示了说出的话
which gives more access to
方便了使用者
people, whether you have hearing
无论是患有听力丧失
loss, in a public setting, or
还是在公共场合
maybe even learning a new
甚至是在学习
language.
一门新语言时
It's like trying to watch a
这就像试图
video or a game intro with the
将音量调到最低
volume turned all the way down,
观看视频或游戏介绍
or trying to read someone's lips
或者读
that aren't looking at you.
没有直视你的人的唇语一样
It feels like you only get about
就像你只能了解
half the story.
故事的一半
So, apps like Kitchen Stories
因此像 Kitchen Stories 这样的 App
have added captions to all of
为所有的烹饪视频
their cooking videos, which is
添加了字幕
great.
做的非常好
OK so along with sight is sound.
说完视觉接着就是听觉
You can ask yourself, are your
你应该问问自己
apps audible?
我的 App 可听吗
So, let's listen to a clip of
让我们再听一遍
the intro design for Carlos V.
关于 Carlos V 的视频片段
video again and listen to the
听听 App 的语音提示
significance of the audible cues
和 VoiceOver
of the app along with VoiceOver
对他操作的
that he's using to navigate.
重要帮助
Now, VoiceOver is a built-in
VoiceOver 是一个内置的
screen reader that speaks the
屏幕阅读器
content on screen for people who
它能将屏幕上的内容读给
may be blind or have low vision.
失明或是视力低下的人
&gt;&gt; Messages.
VoiceOver：信息
ReverbNation.
来自 ReverbNation
Double tap to open.
双击以打开
Text field.
文本框
Dictate.
听写
&gt;&gt; Album will be dropping
Carols：专辑将在 2017 年 4 月 14 日
worldwide on April 14, 2017!
全球发行（感叹号）
Follow our ReverbNation page.
关注我们的 ReverbNation 页面（句号）
&gt;&gt; Done. Successfully shared.
VoiceOver：完成 已成功分享
&gt;&gt; So, we can hear VoiceOver
我们听到了 VoiceOver
navigating the app.
操作 App
The custom sounds of the apps
App 信息的自定义声音功能
messaging feature, and dictation
和输入信息的
to input the message.
听写功能
Altogether, this creates an
这些共同作用让
experience that is accessible to
Carols 可以进行
Carlos.
操作
So, adding thoughtful sounds to
在 App 交互中添加语音
app interactions helps you know
帮助使用者了解
where you are, what you've done,
他们在哪里 做过什么事
what you can do.
可以做什么
Plus, it's just delightful.
这是一种很棒的体验
So, checking out VoiceOver in a
在系统中使用 VoiceOver
system is as easy as asking Siri
非常简单
to turn VoiceOver on and off.
只要告诉 Siri 开启或关闭 VoiceOver 就可以了
But if you don't know the
如果你不知道
VoiceOver's like I have a quick
VoiceOver 是什么样的
demo here.
这里有一个快速 demo
I'll be swiping across the
我会滑动屏幕
screen to advance the selection
在 App 中
through some apps.
进行选择
But then since I know that the
因为我知道
phone app is in my dock, I'm
App 已经在我的 Dock 中了
going to tap the lower left hand
我只需要点按屏幕的左下角
corner of the screen and then
接着
double tap to open.
双击以打开
&gt;&gt; VoiceOver on.
VoiceOver 开启
Mail. No unread emails.
邮件 无未读邮件
Calendar. Monday, June 5.
日历 星期一 6 月 5 日
Photos. Camera.
照片 相机
Dock. Phone.
Dock 通讯录
Phone. Add.
通讯录 添加
Favorites.
收藏
Edit button.
编辑按钮
Amy Frost iPhone button.
Amy Frost iPhone 按钮
&gt;&gt; So, and there are tutorials
Apple 开发人员网站上
and documentation on Apple's
有教程和文稿
developer site to help you
可以帮助你
become even more familiar and to
更熟悉这个功能
be able to support this in your
并在你的 App 中
apps.
支持该功能
Additionally, if you have
除此之外
image-based apps, we need to
如果你有基于图像的 App
allow image descriptions to be
需要允许-图像描述
added at share time by the
被 Poster 添加到 Share time
poster so that VoiceOver can
这样 VoiceOver
have something personalized to
就可以使用个性化内容来
describe the photo with.
描述图像
Otherwise, new in VoiceOver this
此外今年在 VoiceOver 中
year is image analysis to
新推出了图像分析
describe the image contents or
可以描述图像内容和构成
composition, or if type is
或图像上
overlaid on images.
是否有重叠
But a handcrafted description
但一个量身打造的描述
will always be preferred.
总是最合适的
Twitter has done a great job at
Twitter 在添加图像描述选项
adding image description options
到 Tweet 表单中
to their Tweet sheets.
做的很好
So, another area that reduces
另一个减少
hurdles and barriers for apps is
App 障碍的方法就是
integrating with Siri.
与 Siri 相结合
Siri is the ultimate quick
Siri 是进入你 App
access to your app that doesn't
最快的方法
even require looking or holding,
甚至不需要
or touching the screen, with
盯着查看触摸屏幕
this voice activation and speech
只要语音启动
input.
和输入就可以了
It's hands-free and eyes free.
它解放了双手和双眼
I can control my home, send
我可以控制我的家
messages, and even start
发信息
workouts quickly with apps like
甚至使用 Zova 等 App
Zova.
快速开始锻炼
And also, new this year is being
今年 Siri 的新功能
able to type to Siri that is
是可以进行打字输入
available in accessibility
该功能
settings.
在辅助功能设置中可以找到
This gives quick access to
这能够大大方便
someone who may not be able to
那些不能说话的
speak.
使用者
Or maybe you're just in a public
或者-处在公共场所
setting.
的使用者
So, lastly, along with sight and
说完了视觉和听觉
sound, is touch.
最后要说一下触觉
You can ask yourself, are your
问一下自己
apps tactile?
你的 App 是可触的吗
On supported devices adding
在受支持的设备上
haptics provides a way to
添加触觉技术
physically engage people through
会提高人们的
feel.
实际参与感
It gets your attention if sight
在视觉和听觉都无法使用的时候
and sound are not an option.
它会吸引你的注意
But also, provides an
同时也提高了
enhancement for everyone.
每个人的体验
For example, some
比如
system-provided interface
一些系统提供的界面元素
elements such as switches,
如开关
sliders, pickers, index
滑动 选择器
scrubbers provide haptic
滚动条
feedback when we interact with
都在交互时提供-触觉反馈
them to reinforce the action
强调我们正在进行的
that we're doing.
活动
And a haptic on pull to refresh,
下拉刷新也有触觉反馈
let's you know that you've
让你知道你已经
reached the critical threshold
到达了
between scrolling and refreshing
滚动和刷新的界限
that shares a continuous
因为它们是
gesture.
同一个持续的活动
And likewise, with swipe to
滑动和删除
delete.
也是同理
The haptic provides the critical
触觉提醒了
threshold of the accelerated
累计删除和滑动的
delete swipe.
界限
And then another example is
另一个例子是
Siri.
Siri
It uses a success haptic as a
她使用了成功触觉反馈
confirmation that she heard what
确认她已经听到
you said.
你说的话
Or Apple Pay uses visuals
Apple Pay 也使用视觉
haptics and sound with the
触觉和听觉确认
confirmation for the successful
已经成功
purchase.
购买
It feels the way it looks and
它的触觉视觉和听觉
sounds, leaving me with a
让我有信心
confident purchase or payment
购买或支付
[ding].
[ 叮 ]
Now, that's clear.
现在就很清楚了
So, to see if your apps are
要确定你的 App
perceivable, ask yourself is it
是否可感知
legible?
问自己它易读吗
Can I read it?
我能读懂吗
Is it audible?
它可听吗
Is it usable without site?
能够在不看的情况下使用吗
Is it tactile?
可触吗
Can I feel it?
我能感受到吗
Take one away, or even two of
这三点中除去一点或两点
these can I still understand it.
是不是仍然可以理解
And so, now my colleague AJ is
现在我的同事 AJ
going to talk about what they
将介绍
did in the Maps Team this year,
今年地图组的成果
applying some of these methods.
他们应用了上述的一些方法
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Thank you Caroline.
谢谢你 Caroline
Good morning, everyone.
大家早上好
In Maps we collaborated closely
在地图中
with Caroline and the platform
我们与 Caroline 和平台组
team.
密切合作
And this year we put into
今年我们实践了
practice a lot of what she's
很多今天她
covered today.
演讲涵盖的内容
Now, before we get into a few of
在具体到几个例子
those examples, and think about
思考如何
how to design with integrity,
进行正直设计之前
we're going to take a short
我们先来
diversion.
放松一下
It's going to add a couple of
花几分钟
minutes to our ETA.
在我们的 ETA 上
We've used maps for thousands of
在过去的数千年间我们一直使用地图
years to plan, direct, to travel
规划导航旅行
and to help us explore the
帮助我们探索
world.
世界
And maps of the past, like this
以前的地图
one, beautiful as they remain,
像这个依然非常精美
were not accessible at all.
但完全不实用
You can't zoom on this map
不使用放大镜
without a magnifying glass, and
你无法缩放地图
you couldn't orient yourself
也不能在没有指南针的情况下
upon it without a compass.
定位自己
In face the only manipulating
实际上你唯一能对它做的
you could do would be to fold
就是把它
it.
折叠起来
So, as our understanding of the
随着我们对世界理解的加深
world has improved, so have our
我们的地图
maps.
也有相应的改进
Today, your map understands
如今你的地图
where you are.
知道你的位置
It knows the direction you're
知道你面对的
facing.
方向
It knows the device you're
知道你使用的设备
using, and it's equipped with
你还可以个性化的
your individual preferences.
设置地图
It's updated every day with new
它每天都会根据新信息
information.
进行更新
And you can search it.
你可以进行搜索
You can mark it indestructibly
进行非破坏性的标注
and make it your own.
将它个性化
It can take you places in real
以便它能实时读取你的位置
time, avoiding traffic,
避开交通拥堵
And in iOS 11, you can even see
在 iOS 11 中
inside venues.
你甚至可以看到内部道路
The point is, today our mediums
重点是如今我们的媒介
are so versatile, they provide
十分万能
us with the incredible
才给我们提供了
opportunity.
如此惊人的机会
So, when I joined Maps, I
当我加入地图时
remember thinking a lot about
我记得我在想
how crazy it felt to see inside.
看到内部运作是多么疯狂的事情啊
Like looking through a keyhole
就像透过锁孔往里看一样
and stepping through this icon,
我从未想过
I cannot have imagined the
在图标背后
operation I saw behind it.
我将看见怎样的操作
I took it almost completely for
我把一切都想得
granted.
理所当然
And everyone who uses our apps
每一个使用我们 App 的人
are the same way.
都这么想
They don't care how hard it was
他们并不在乎
to build.
构建这个 App 有多困难
It's not important that it works
Johnny Appleseed 或 Jane Doe
for Johnny Appleseed or Jane
能不能用这个 App
Doe.
并不重要
What's important is that it
重要的是
works for me.
我可以用
Can I use it?
我能使用它吗
Imagine going to the movies.
想象一下你走进电影院
You bought your ticket and your
带着你的电影票
excited to watch the film.
和观影的激动心情
The theater's packed.
影院人满为患
You get to your seat and there's
你找到了自己的位子
a pillar in front of it,
但是面前有一根柱子
completely blocking your view.
完全挡住了视线
I'm pretty sure I'm not going to
那我非常确定
come back to that cinema.
我不会再去那家影院了
And I'm no longer just a regular
如果类似的事情
Maps user, not that there's any
发生在地图中
such thing.
我也不会再使用了
We're trying to build a map of
我们试图
the entire world and it's a big
制作的是整个世界的地图
and diverse place.
每个地方都各不相同
Like you, I'm on a team
像你一样
responsible for everyone's
我所在的组
experience.
要为每个人的体验负责
So, coming back to simplicity
所以我们要回归简单
and perceivability.
和感知性
Maps are not exact replicas of
地图不是对环境的
environments.
完全复制
Sometimes photographic detail is
有时详细准确的细节
useful.
很有用
But most people don't find the
但大部分人认为
satellite view practical in
在日常生活中
everyday life.
卫星图像并不非常实用
We use simplified abstracted
我们使用简单抽象的图形表达
representations, designed to be
它们被设计得
easy to understand and faster
易于理解
for us to process to help us
让我们更快地处理
orient ourselves more quickly.
并且定位自己
And it's why we provide a
这就是为什么我们也提供
transit map too.
交通地图
Where we suppress some elements,
在交通地图中我们压缩了一些元素
like places or minor roads,
比如某些场所和支路
which aren't as relevant to you
因为你在使用交通系统时
once you're using transit.
这些信息不是非常相关
And we do all this for
我们的所作所为都是为了
simplicity.
简洁
And we make sure our maps are
我们确保地图是
understandable.
可理解的
Visually, audibly, and through
是视觉听觉
haptic feedback.
和触觉的反馈
We put a lot of care into
我们花了很多精力
keeping the navigation screen as
使操作屏幕
simple as possible.
尽可能的简单
The most important information
最重要的信息
available at a glance.
一眼就可以看到
So, you can understand quickly
所以你可以快速了解
and stay focused on the road.
并且专注路况
And while you're walking or
当你步行
taking transit, audible
或通勤时
directions spoken clearly.
语音指导也非常清楚
&gt;&gt; Starting route to San Jose
开始规划去 San Jose
McEnery Convention Center.
McEnery Convention Center 的路线
&gt;&gt; Imagine if Siri mumbled these
想象一下如果 Siri
instructions incomprehensibly.
喃喃地说出这些难以理解的指示
Because isn't that kind of the
因为它并不等同于
equivalent to small, blurry
简短模糊的
information.
信息
And on your wrist, while your
当你把手机放在口袋里时
phone is in your pocket,
你手腕上
different tactic sensations to
不同的触觉反馈
inform which way to turn and
会通知你转弯的方向
when.
和时间
Altogether for perceivability.
合在一起就是可感知的
It's legible, audible, and
因为它是易读可听
tactile.
可触的
And you can use any one of these
你也可以单独使用
distinctly.
其中的一个
Integrity is something different
正直是一个不同的
conceptually.
概念
We do things for simplicity and
我们简化是为了
to improve perceivability.
提高可感性
But we do things with integrity.
但我们同时也需要正直
The state of being whole and
这是一种完整专心的
undivided.
状态
When we say someone has
当我们说一个人很正直的时候
integrity with think of them as
我们都认为他们
being honest with an admirable
是诚实的
moral compass.
有着令人钦佩的道德罗盘
So, when we consider that the
所以当我们
people who need our services the
考虑到最需要我们服务的人时
most, might be the ones who find
可能他们
them the hardest to use, how do
会觉得使用非常困难
we design with integrity.
如何做正直设计呢
Well, as designers and
作为设计师
developers, we take
和开发人员
responsibility.
我们肩负责任
When architects build spaces
但建筑师设计建造时
today, they make sure they're
他们会确保
accessible for everyone because
所有人都能够享受
it's a human right.
因为这是人权
And when designer draw beautiful
当设计师画出精美的车时
cars, they still have to adhere
他们仍然需要遵守
to regulations created for human
为人们的安全
safety.
而设立的规则
So, when we design digital
因此当我们设计数码产品时
products, we have to hold
我们也要对它们的
ourselves accountable for their
可用性
accessibility too.
负责
Because when we don't we're
因为如果不这样的话
deciding who's important.
我们就没有做到一视同仁
Last year for iOS 10, we
在去年的 iOS 10 中
redesigned Maps from the ground
我们重新设计了地图
up.
推倒重来
Making it clearer, simpler, easy
让它更简单更明确
to use, and faster.
更易用也更快
And it was a big undertaking.
这是个大工程
We opened the door on
我们打开了
accessibility, but we didn't go
可用性的大门
that far along the corridor.
但只到达了走廊
It was a busy year.
去年很忙碌
But in iOS 11 we did take
在 iOS 11 中我们确实
responsibility, and we made it a
负起了责任
priority, leveraging the new
优先考虑了可用性
UIKit frameworks and following
我们利用了新的 UIKit 框架
the principles that Caroline
并遵循了 Caroline
outlined today.
今天提出的原则
Making as much text dynamic as
让尽可能多的文本动态化
possible, displaying the same
与默认 UI 显示相同
amount of text as the default
数量的文本
UI, using as much of the screen
利用宽度尽可能展示
width for text.
文本
Search is a core component of
搜索是地图的核心组成部分
Maps and now it's easier for
现在所有人
everyone to use.
都能够轻松使用
But it's not always just as
但这并不总是像
simple as increasing the font
调大字体
size.
那样简单
And you might be thinking, hang
你可能会想 等等
on, I can see some truncation in
我在屏幕快照中
these screenshots.
看到了一些截断
This breaks the principles we're
这违背了我们讨论的原则
talking about, and you're right.
你是对的
But sometimes we have to make
但有时我们要根据情境
choices based on context.
做出选择
Like, on the right screen here
就像右侧屏幕
the top of the card has a fixed
信息卡顶端有一个固定的
header.
标题
So, if we didn't truncate, the
如果我们不截断
route options beneath would not
下方的路线选项
be scrollable.
将无法滚动
Now, this is the card for a
这是一个地方的
place.
信息卡
They're used in different
他们在 iOS 中很多不同的情境下
context across iOS, including
被使用
Spotlight, Safari, and Siri.
包括 Spotlight Safari 和 Siri
And from here you start
你要从这里开始操作
navigation, make a call to check
打电话
on your reservation.
核对你的预定
Or even have a look at what's
甚至看一下
inside.
里面是什么样子的
Things everyone might like to
这是每个人都想做的
do.
事情
So, let's take a closer look at
让我们近距离的看看
some of the components of this
该设计的一些组成部分
design, like the title block.
比如标题块
We use this with search results
我们也用它显示搜索结果
too and last year we truncated
去年我们截断了
the title for long place names
长地名的标题
instead of wrapping.
而不是进行绕排
But with a big of UIKit magic,
但借助 UIKit 的力量后
this year, now it does this.
今年我们做到了这样
Which is actually pretty cool.
实际上非常酷
And the component is more
这个组成部分
effective and robust because of
因此变得更有效
it.
也更具鲁棒性了
And we made some changes to the
今年我们调整了地点信息卡
place card this year to improve
增强了
hierarchy including this
层级包括
secondary row of actions.
第二栏活动
And we need to accommodate a
我们需要在这里包含
maximum of five options here.
最多五个选项
Like these.
就像这样
So, on an iPhone 7, in English,
因此在 iPhone 7 的英语版本中
That was such a cheap joke.
开个玩笑
On iPhone 7, in English this
在 iPhone 7 的英语版本中
works and we can fit five in a
我们成功做到了
row.
连续放五个选项
But how do we handle it with
但我们要如何对它使用
dynamic type?
动态类型呢
Because we can't just increase
因为我们不能仅仅
the font size.
增大字号
But we could stack the UI
我们要巧妙地
elements smartly.
堆叠 UI 组成部分
And all the way up the scale.
扩大规模
Internationalization is a form
国际化
of accessibility too.
也是可用性的一种形式
And it brings its own
它也面临自己的
challenges.
挑战
So, how about these labels in
这些意大利语的标签
Italian.
看上去如何
OK, they're a bit longer.
好吧 它们有一点长
So, if we go back down to
如果我们回到
default size, oh, but the label
默认大小
is truncating.
哦 标签被截断了
And the label is important.
标签是很重要的
We should try not to truncate it
我们应该尽力在任何大小时
at any size.
都不截断它
But we could apply a similar
我们可以应用与这
technique like this.
类似的技术
And now, they remain clear and
现在标签就清清楚楚
uncompromised.
没有截断了
Adaptive design based on a
适应性设计是
user's language and UI settings.
根据用户的语言和 UI 设置
And now it works better across
现在它在不同大小设备上
different device sizes too.
也能够正常运行
And for these actions at the
对于信息卡底端的活动
bottom of the card, as well as
以及
all of the content, we reflowed
所有内容
the labels and scaled the icons.
我们重新安排了标签并缩放了图标
Using vector assets, so there's
使用的是向量素材
no pixilation.
因此没有像素点
And of course, we made all the
当然我们为所有的
labels VoiceOver enabled.
标签启用了 VoiceOver
And in Maps, we hung out with
在地图中
Siri as well.
我们也结合了 Siri
So, there are more complex
所以有很多比我刚刚展示的
challenges than the ones I just
更复杂的
illustrated.
挑战
And it's easier not to take
如果不承担责任
responsibility.
会比较轻松
But challenges are rewarding.
但挑战会带来回报
And that's how I ended up;
这就是我获得的
challenges are fun and
挑战很有趣
rewarding.
并且回报丰厚
And that's why I ended up
这就是为什么
standing here today.
我今天站在这里
Designing for everyone is a
为每个人设计是一个过程
process that can bring a deeper
能让你对你的产品
understanding of your product
和它的目的
and its purpose.
有更深的理解
One of the few effective keys to
是解决设计问题时
the design problem.
有效的关键因素之一
The ability of the designer to
设计师能够识别出
recognize as many of the
可能制约因素的
constraints possible, their
能力越强
willingness and enthusiasm for
他们会越愿意越有激情
working within these
在制约内
constraints.
工作
Because out of constraints come
因为打破制约
great solutions.
需要很好的解决方案
And if we're designing just for
如果我们只为通用设置而设计
default settings, we're not
我们就不能
doing it right.
很好地实现
By trying to do better than
但在试图做到的时候
that, we make ourselves better.
我们也在提升自己
And we really learned an awful
这一年我们真的
lot this year.
学到了很多
So, secondly after we decide to
在我们决定
take responsibility, we need to
负起责任之后
think about empathy.
我们需要考虑共情
The ability to understand
这是理解他人的
people.
能力
To recognize their wants,
弄清他们的需求
desires, and feelings.
需要和感觉
People that are not you --
这些人不是你
because nobody else is.
因为没有第二个你
So, let's take a look at a few
让我们看几个
made-up examples that might be
可能更贴近生活的
closer to home.
例子
Newspapers.
报纸
Never been accessible.
从来都不易用
There's something nice to
坐下来看报纸
sitting down with a newspaper,
是一种享受
but not if you can't read it.
但如果你不能阅读
If your vision isn't perfect,
或者视力不佳
reading one of these has always
进行阅读将始终是
been a challenge.
一个挑战
And a lot of you create
你们中有很多人
platforms for content that's
创造的内容平台
consumed the world over.
过度消费了世界
Platforms with the capabilities
这些平台
to improve the readability of
有能力
our content, relatively and
相对地提高内容的
automatically.
可读性
And platforms, which can be
也有一些平台
navigated and understood through
可以让那些不能通过视觉阅读的人
sound for those who can't read
通过声音操作导航
visually.
和理解
And we read a lot on our iPhones
我们在 iPhone 和 iPad
or iPads.
上经常阅读
Sometimes it's good news, other
这件事有好的一面
times it's bad news.
也有不好的一面
Or, depending on where you look,
取决于你的视角
it could be fake news, like
有一些可能是假新闻
these revelations about Lorem
比如说被揭露的
ipsum.
假文
So, here's the same article with
这里有一些相同的文章
some visual considerations for
展现了关于动态类型的
dynamic type.
视觉重点
The headline is moved outside
标题被移到了
the hero image for better
英雄图像外
contrast and for practicality.
对比性更强也更实用
And the content is readable at
内容是以我喜欢的字号
my preferred size.
显示可读的
And it still looks great.
看上去仍然不错
But what if you couldn't read a
但如果你读不懂
price tag?
标价呢
What would the experience of
那买东西会变成
buying things be like?
什么样
You can't tap on a price tag to
你无法轻按标价来
hear an audio cue, but on an
听语音提示
iPhone, iPad, or Mac you can do
但在 iPhone iPad 或 Mac上
exactly that and more.
你却不仅能这么做
So, here we are shopping for
假设现在我们正在买
fresh, delicious, emoji-fied
新鲜美味的
fruit.
水果
And there's a two-column layout
在默认设置中
at default settings.
是两栏式布局
So, if we turn up dynamic types
如果我们开启动态类型
a bit, we could reflow the
我们可以重新安排内容
content into one linear list.
把它变成线性列表
Similar to how you would on a
与你如何
responsive website between
在桌面和移动断点上
desktop and mobile breakpoints.
对响应性网站的处理类似
Giving enough space to elements
给组成部分留出足够的空间
to make them simpler and easier
让他们简单轻松的
to pass.
通过
And here's our product page for
这是菠萝的
this pineapple.
产品页面
Adapting your layout
适当的调整你的布局
appropriately makes sure the
确保
most important actions are
最重要的活动可以
available immediately.
立即可用
So, again if we bump up the
因此如果我们增加
dynamic type that's working
动态类型
pretty well.
它会运行得很好
But, let's turn it up to the
让我们调到
maximum.
最大
Nice, but is there more we can
很好 但我们可以做出什么
do here?
改进呢
If we scroll the card, we can
如果我们滚动信息卡
see the most desired actions are
就能看见最需要的活动
a little bit far way.
离得很远
So, maybe we'd consider swapping
因此我们可以考虑在内容中
them in this context.
调换它们
Yes. And that's definitely
是的这样就绝对
better.
好多了
Well, what about music,
那么音乐
podcasts, stories, sound?
播客 故事 声音又是怎样的呢
Audio content is great because
音频内容很好
it plays over the air, or your
因为它能通过耳机
headphones.
或者直接外放
You don't need a UI to be
你不需要为它
entertained by it.
设计 UI
But you do need a UI to be able
但你需要发现
to discover it.
音频内容的 UI
And in the new podcast and music
在 iOS 11 新的播客和音乐中
apps on iOS 11, the content
内容会根据个人偏好
adapts to your preferences and
进行调整
can be used with VoiceOver, so
也可以用 VoiceOver
everyone can access it.
因此对每个人都可用
Now, finally potential energy.
终于说到了最后的潜在能量
Unlocking potential.
解锁潜能
If we make more things possible
如果我们为更多的人
for more types of people, more
使上述内容成为可能
things can happen.
那么会发生更多精彩的事情
Awesome things like iconic
比如
albums or pioneering science.
代表专辑或先锋科学
Or miraculous things like
或者像
remembering your friends'
记住你朋友生日
birthdays.
这样的神奇事情
Simple things like sending a
和向
gift or a message to a loved
你爱的人
one.
寄礼物和发送信息这样简单的事
Can anyone read that?
有人可以读吗
We're reliant on language and
我们对语言的依赖
our remarkable use of it is
和频繁使用
perhaps the primary reason for
可能是人类作为物种
our success as a species.
成功的主要原因
Be it through colors, text,
接着是颜色 文本
sound, or signs.
声音或符号
And what about now?
现在呢
German speakers in the room are
我身前是
one step ahead of us.
说德语的人
If we don't communicate in
如果我们不能以
everyone's language, how can we
对方的语言交流
help them accomplish things?
我们要如何帮助他们完成任务呢
Without understanding, we can't
没有理解
create any value at all.
我们无法创造任何价值
I read an amazing article
我在这周的早期时候
earlier this week called, "The
读到了一篇精彩的文章
Thoughts of a Spider Web" by
是 Joshua Sokol 所著
Joshua Sokol.
《蜘蛛网的思考》
And in it there was an example
其中有一个例子
about how bees use ultraviolet
是关于蜜蜂如何使用
vision to find flowers that have
紫外线找到
also evolved ultraviolet
同样进化出
markings.
紫外线标记的花
And beside it a quote which
文中还有这样一句话
said, "if you don't have those
“世界上不能接受信息
receptors that part of the world
的部分
simply doesn't exist."
相当于不存在”
Design that includes everyone is
为每个人的设计
not good design, it's great
不再是好的设计
design.
而是杰出的设计
So, design with integrity.
因此正直设计
Take responsibility, caring
负起责任
about everyone's experience, not
关心每一个人的体验
just your own.
而不是只有你自己
And be empathetic considering
做到感同身受
the perspectives of others who
在别人的角度思考问题
interact with the world in
他们与世界交互的方法
different ways than you do.
与你不一样
And understand that by doing so
并且理解这么做
we can help unlock potential, in
我们能够解锁潜能
tiny and huge ways.
无论是微观上还是宏观上
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; So, together we can strive
总的来说我们要在 App 中
for simplicity and
力求简洁
perceivability in our apps.
和感知性
And do it all with integrity for
并且正直设计
making good apps great.
让好的 App 更加杰出
I encourage you to start now.
希望大家现在行动
Go home and audit your apps.
回家检查你的 App
Start conversations with your
与你的团队
team and people who use your
和使用你 App 的人
apps.
进行交流
And most importantly schedule
最重要的是
time to see it all the way into
抽出时间查看 App
customers' hands.
到顾客手中的全过程
And lastly do it proudly.
最后自豪地完成它
We can give everyone the chance
我们能够让每个人都有机会
to be surprised, delighted, feel
感到惊讶 欣喜
good, and empowered.
愉快和充满力量
We especially as designers would
作为设计师我们尤其喜欢
always like things to line up
正确排列的事物
just right, but you can't
但你不能控制
control every line break.
每一个换行
You can't control how someone
你不能控制
will need to personalize their
别人需要如何个性化他们的体验
experience because everyone is
因为每个人都是
different.
不同的
And let's celebrate that.
让我们为此欢呼吧
&gt;&gt; We're really proud of what
我们为自己今年在
we've achieved in Maps this
地图中取得的成就深感自豪
year, but there's more to do and
但要做的还有很多
we're going to keep going,
我们会继续努力
because a map is never finished.
因为地图是永远不会完成的
And everyone wants to find their
每一个人都想找到他们的
way.
路
So, we're designing for everyone
因此我们为每个人设计
and we really hope you'll join
我们真诚希望你们能够
us on this mission.
加入到这项活动中来
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Now, there's a lot of great
有许多强大的功能
features that we couldn't cover
今天我们没能提及
today, so please check out
请前往
Apple's accessibility website
Apple 辅助功能网站查看
for many other great ways to
其它的使
make your apps accessible for
所有人都能
everyone.
使用你 App 的方法
And you can watch this talk
你可以在 Apple 开发人员网站的
again at this URL at the Apple
这个网址
developer site, or on the WWDC
或 WWDC App 上
app.
再次观看本节会议
And later today in this same
今天晚些时候你们可以在同一场地的
room check out "Design Across
“跨平台设计”一节中
Platform" session for details on
找到关于
how your app is best presented
如何让你的 App
on each platform and for
在每个平台上得到最佳呈现的详细信息
implementation details on all
关于所有今天讲到的
the new iOS 11 dynamic type APIs
新 iOS 11 动态类型 API 的
we spoke about today, please
实现细节
check out the "Building Apps
请关注明天下午的
with Dynamic Type" tomorrow
“构建使用动态类型的
afternoon.
App”一节
Otherwise, please check out
除此之外
these other great talks on
请前往 developer.apple.com
developer.apple.com or the WWDC
或  WWDC App
app.
查看其他会议内容
Thank you.
谢谢大家